export const JavascriptQuestions =[
   {
       type:'multi_choice',
       question:'what is the type of null',
       answers:['undefined','boolean','object','null'],
       right:'object'
   },
   {
       type:'true_false',
       question:`"Const" is global scoped`,
       right:'false'
       
   },
   {
    type:'fill_blank',
    question:'Javascript is',
    right:'scripting'
},
{
    type:'multi_select',
    question:'Javascript is ',
    answers:['multithreaded','singlethread','asynchronous','low level'],
    right:'singlethread'
}
]
export const htmlQuestions =[
    {
        type:'multi_choice',
        question:'what is HTML',
        answers:['undefined','boolean','object','null'],
        right:'object'
    },
    {
        type:'true_false',
        question:`"Const" is global scoped`,
        right:false
        
    },
    {
     type:'fill_blank',
     question:'Javascript is',
     right:'scripting'
 },
 {
     type:'multi_select',
     question:'Javascript is',
     right:'scripting'
 }
 ]
 export const cssQuestions =[
    {
        type:'multi_choice',
        question:'what is CSs',
        answers:['undefined','boolean','object','null'],
        right:'object'
    },
    {
        type:'true_false',
        question:`"Const" is global scoped`,
        right:false
        
    },
    {
     type:'fill_blank',
     question:'Javascript is',
     right:'scripting'
 },
 {
     type:'multi_select',
     question:'Javascript is',
     right:'scripting'
 }
 ]